{
    "id": "20_Science_169",
    "claim": "There is an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehiclesIt is one of the most inspiring deaths in cinema. The farewell of the life of replicant Batty in the first Blade Runner. Rutger Hauer's tears are a counterpoint to his own ferocious existence.'I've seen things you wouldn't believe..\". In that film by  he imagined a dystopian  in which, however, cars were seen flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?Now we see what is happening in Catalonia, or in the United Kingdom. And many other things we wouldn't believe if someone had told us years ago. It is worth taking air and thinking of others who, although with less informational urgency, can help us to create a better world. In these innovations that are difficult to grasp in a term as limited as 'digitization ', electric vehicles are particularly exciting. New productive, labor and social relationships in which, sometimes, the important thing is not the product or the service but the channel or the support. Satisfaction is no longer in what we enjoy but in how we do it. It's not about cars but what moves them. Let us be driven autonomously, safer and free of emissions. A company led changes in personal computers forty years ago and, after multiple vicissitudes, resurfaced to the forefront to offer much more than desktop equipment. Many problems in production, in patent protection, in market entry but.. finally, the triumph of an idea. Another company leads the technology for the electric vehicle, but offers dreams beyond it. Working to accelerate the global transition to sustainable energy, it shows real achievements and the promise of what may come 'lead 'to a sustainable and advanced reality. In a city like Paris there will be no diesel powered cars running on the Champs-Elysees beyond  or gasoline after . Spain is lagging behind in this area, which is a matter of great concern, with a relatively low enrolment rate and city pollution values exceeding those allowed at European level. There is an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehicles in our country, as well as to review car taxation to discourage the most polluting vehicles. More and more brands  albeit unevenly developed  are slowly joining the electric automotive industry. Innovation focuses on self-driving and traffic safety. The EU is, in fact, in the final stages of regulatory development in order to promote certain changes, for example, by increasing charging points, in the Community territory. These innovations lead to disruption in the labour market where there will be challenges and opportunities. These are companies that are factories of ideas, with a tremendous vertical integration. Where a fuse can be the subject of discussion or the problem that must be solved and where they put their concentration hundreds of minds at once. Where hope is shared. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "elpais.com",
    "date": "23/10/2017",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "There is an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehiclesIt is one of the most Another company in the technology for the electric vehicle .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on the urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehicles?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why is there an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.8254,
                    "answers": "that There is an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero - emission vehiclesIt|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the technology for electric vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.6273,
                    "answers": "the most Another company in the technology for the electric vehicle|pobj\tin the technology for the electric vehicle|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4717,
                    "answers": "one of the most Another company in the technology for the electric vehicle|attr\tof the most Another company in the technology for the electric vehicle|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that the technology for the electric vehicle vehicles is the technology for the electric vehicle vehicles?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What technology did elpais.com use for the electric vehicle vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.773,
                    "answers": "that the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the technology for electric vehicle vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.762,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt the technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt|ROOT\ton 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe technology for the electric vehicle vehiclesIt|nsubj\tfor the electric vehicle vehiclesIt|prep\tthe|det\telectric|amod\telectric vehicle|compound\tthe electric vehicle vehiclesIt|pobj\tthe|det\tfor the electric vehicle vehiclesIt|prep\tthe|det\telectric|amod\telectric vehicle|compound\tthe electric vehicle vehiclesIt|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Rutger Hauer's tears are a counterpoint to own ferocious existence.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that Rutger Hauer's tears are a counterpoint to his own ferocious existence?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hauer say about his existence?",
                    "score": 0.6882,
                    "answers": "to own ferocious existence|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Rutger Hauer's tears?",
                    "score": 0.6334,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Rutger Hauer 's tears are a counterpoint to own ferocious existence|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the existence of Rutger Hauer?",
                    "score": 0.6246,
                    "answers": "own ferocious existence|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Hauer and Hauer?",
                    "score": 0.5575,
                    "answers": "Rutger Hauer 's|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'I've seen things you wouldn't believe..\".",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that 'I've seen things you wouldn't believe'?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.6834,
                    "answers": "'ve|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about things you wouldn't believe?",
                    "score": 0.6738,
                    "answers": "things you would n't believe|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website \"lpais.com\" say about it?",
                    "score": 0.6234,
                    "answers": "n't|neg\tyou would n't believe|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5077,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that ' I 've seen things you would n't believe .. \"|ROOT\tthat|mark\t'|punct\tI|nsubj\tthat ' I 've seen things you would n't believe|ccomp\tyou|nsubj\twould|aux\t..|punct\t\"|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the claims made by elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5003,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In that film by  Rutger Hauer's imagined a dystopian  in which, however, cars were seen flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?Now we see what is happening in Catalonia, or in the United Kingdom.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on Rutger Hauer's film?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Rutger Hauer say about cars flying?",
                    "score": 0.6827,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that In that film by   Rutger Hauer 's imagined a dystopian   in which , however , cars were seen flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?Now we see what is happening in Catalonia , or in the United Kingdom|ROOT\ton 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tIn that film by|prep\tthat|det\tby|prep\tthat In that film by   Rutger Hauer 's imagined a dystopian   in which , however , cars were seen flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?Now we see what is happening in Catalonia , or in the United Kingdom|dep\t's|dep\ta|det\ta dystopian   in which , however , cars were seen flying|dep\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\t,|punct\thowever|advmod\t,|punct\tcars|nsubjpass\twere|auxpass\tin which , however , cars were seen flying|relcl\tflying|xcomp\tCan|aux\ta|det\ta car|nsubj\tan|det\tan element of social inspiration and change?Now|attr\tof social inspiration and change?Now|prep\tsocial|amod\tsocial inspiration and change?Now|pobj\tand|cc\twe|nsubj\twhat|nsubj\tis|aux\twhat is happening in Catalonia , or in the United Kingdom|ccomp\tin Catalonia , or in the United Kingdom|prep\t,|punct\tor|cc\tin the United Kingdom|conj\tthe|det\tUnited|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Hauer say about flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?",
                    "score": 0.6287,
                    "answers": "Rutger Hauer 's imagined a dystopian   in which , however , cars were seen flying Can a car be an element of social inspiration and change?Now|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And many other things we wouldn't believe if someone had told us years ago.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that many other things we wouldn't believe if someone had told us years ago?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.6283,
                    "answers": "we would n't believe if someone had told us years ago|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website \"lpais.com\" say about it?",
                    "score": 0.5229,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|det\tAnd|cc\tmany|amod\tother|amod\tthat And many other things we would n't believe if someone had told us years ago|dobj\twe|nsubj\twould|aux\tn't|neg\tif|mark\tsomeone|nsubj\thad|aux\tif someone had told us years ago|advcl\tus|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4535,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that And many other things we would n't believe if someone had told us years ago|ROOT\tyears|npadvmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It is worth taking air and thinking of others who, although with less informational urgency, can help us to create a better world.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that it is worth taking air and thinking of others who can help us to create a better world?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of taking air and thinking of others who, but with less informational urgency, can help us create a better world?",
                    "score": 0.5653,
                    "answers": "although with less informational urgency|advcl\tless informational urgency|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4442,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tand|cc\t,|punct\talthough|mark\t,|punct\tus|nsubj\tto|aux\ta|det\tbetter|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In these innovations Spain to grasp in a term as limited as 'digitization ', electric vehicles are particularly exciting.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What term did elpais.com use to describe electric vehicles?",
                    "answer": "'digitization"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the technology of electric vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.765,
                    "answers": "electric|amod\telectric vehicles|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to digitize electric vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.7637,
                    "answers": "digitization|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of the term \"digitization\" for electric vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.7395,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of digitization?",
                    "score": 0.6245,
                    "answers": "In these innovations Spain to grasp in a term as limited as ' digitization '|prep\tthese innovations Spain to grasp in a term as limited as ' digitization '|pobj\tSpain to grasp in a term as limited as ' digitization '|relcl\tin a term as limited as ' digitization '|prep\ta term as limited as ' digitization '|pobj\tas ' digitization '|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of digitization?",
                    "score": 0.6165,
                    "answers": "as limited as ' digitization '|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "New productive, labor and social relationships in which, sometimes, the important thing is not the product or the service but the channel or the support.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on New productive, labor and social relationships on 23/10/2017?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about new productive, labor and social relationships?",
                    "score": 0.638,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthe important thing|nsubj\tin which , sometimes , the important thing is not the product or the service but the channel or the support|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many social relationships does elpais.com have?",
                    "score": 0.5475,
                    "answers": "social|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Satisfaction is no longer in what we enjoy but in how we do it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did elpais.com report that Satisfaction is no longer in what we enjoy but in?",
                    "answer": "how we do it"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about Satisfaction?",
                    "score": 0.753,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tno|neg\tno longer|advmod\twhat|dobj\twe|nsubj\twhat we enjoy|pcomp\tbut|cc\tin how we do it|conj\thow|advmod\twe|nsubj\thow we do it|pcomp\tit|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Satisfaction and Satisfaction?",
                    "score": 0.7455,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Satisfaction is no longer in what we enjoy but in how we do it|ROOT\tSatisfaction|nsubj\tthat Satisfaction is no longer in what we enjoy but in how we do it|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of Satisfaction?",
                    "score": 0.7411,
                    "answers": "in what we enjoy but in how we do it|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's not about cars but what moves cars .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that It's not about cars but what moves cars?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about cars?",
                    "score": 0.7214,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that It 's not about cars but what moves cars|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that tracks cars moving?",
                    "score": 0.6669,
                    "answers": "what|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between cars and cars?",
                    "score": 0.6233,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthat It 's not about cars but what moves cars|ccomp\tnot|neg\tabout cars but what moves cars|prep\tcars but what moves cars|pobj\tcars|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the website \"lpais.com\"?",
                    "score": 0.5598,
                    "answers": "what moves cars|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5358,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tIt|nsubj\tbut|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Let us be driven autonomously, safer and free of emissions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that Let us be driven autonomously, safer and free of emissions?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about emissions?",
                    "score": 0.8032,
                    "answers": "free of emissions|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of being driven autonomously and free of emissions?",
                    "score": 0.7705,
                    "answers": "autonomously , safer and free of emissions|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the emissions of the United States?",
                    "score": 0.7339,
                    "answers": "of emissions|prep\temissions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4915,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Let us be driven autonomously , safer and free of emissions|ROOT\ton 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tthat Let us be driven autonomously , safer and free of emissions|ccomp\tus|nsubjpass\tbe|auxpass\t,|punct\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "A company led changes in personal computers forty years ago and, after multiple vicissitudes, resurfaced to the forefront to offer much more than desktop equipment.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that a company led changes in personal computers forty years ago?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What company led changes in personal computers 40 years ago?",
                    "score": 0.8396,
                    "answers": "A|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of equipment is available for personal computers today?",
                    "score": 0.7536,
                    "answers": "desktop equipment|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much more computer equipment does elpais.com offer than desktop equipment?",
                    "score": 0.6974,
                    "answers": "much more than desktop equipment|dobj\tthan desktop equipment|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many vicissitudes were there in personal computers fifty years ago?",
                    "score": 0.6833,
                    "answers": "after multiple vicissitudes|prep\tmultiple vicissitudes|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of computers did elpais.com develop?",
                    "score": 0.6733,
                    "answers": "desktop|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Many problems in production, in patent protection, in market entry but.. finally, the triumph of an idea.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that many problems in production, in patent protection, in market entry but finally, the triumph of an idea?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is patent protection?",
                    "score": 0.7027,
                    "answers": "in patent protection , in market entry but .. finally , the triumph of an idea|conj\tpatent|compound\tpatent protection|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many problems were there in production, in patent protection, in market entry and patent protection?",
                    "score": 0.6841,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is market entry?",
                    "score": 0.6164,
                    "answers": "market entry|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the triumph of an idea?",
                    "score": 0.6003,
                    "answers": "in production , in patent protection , in market entry but .. finally , the triumph of an idea|prep\tin market entry but .. finally , the triumph of an idea|conj\tthe triumph of an idea|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the result of market entry?",
                    "score": 0.587,
                    "answers": "market|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Another company leads the technology for the electric vehicle, but offers dreams beyond it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that another company leads the technology for the electric vehicle but offers dreams beyond it?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What company leads the technology for the electric vehicle but offers dreams beyond it?",
                    "score": 0.6726,
                    "answers": "Another|det\tAnother company|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4738,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Another company leads the technology for the electric vehicle , but offers dreams beyond it|ROOT\ton 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tthat Another company leads the technology for the electric vehicle , but offers dreams beyond it|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe technology for the electric vehicle|dobj\tfor the electric vehicle|prep\tthe|det\telectric|amod\tthe electric vehicle|pobj\t,|punct\tbut|cc\toffers dreams beyond it|conj\tdreams beyond it|dobj\tbeyond it|prep\tit|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Working to accelerate the global transition to sustainable energy, it shows real achievements and the promise of what may come 'lead 'to a sustainable and advanced reality.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com call the promise of what may come to a sustainable and advanced reality?",
                    "answer": "'lead"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the achievements of the global transition to sustainable energy?",
                    "score": 0.7055,
                    "answers": "Working to accelerate the global transition to sustainable energy|advcl\tsustainable energy|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the promise of what may come to a sustainable and advanced reality?",
                    "score": 0.5792,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthe global transition to sustainable energy|dobj\tof what may come ' lead ' to a sustainable and advanced reality|prep\twhat may come ' lead ' to a sustainable and advanced reality|pcomp\tto a sustainable and advanced reality|prep\ta sustainable and advanced reality|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In a city like Paris there will be no diesel powered cars running on the Champs-Elysees beyond  or gasoline after .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that there will be no diesel powered cars running on the Champs-Elysees?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are diesel powered cars running on the Champs-Elysees?",
                    "score": 0.8884,
                    "answers": "like Paris|prep\twill|aux\tdiesel|npadvmod\tdiesel powered|amod\trunning on the Champs - Elysees|acl\ton the Champs - Elysees|prep\tthe Champs - Elysees|pobj\tor gasoline after|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many diesel powered cars are there on the Champs-Elysees?",
                    "score": 0.7362,
                    "answers": "that|mark\ta|det\tthe|det\tChamps|compound\t-|punct\tbeyond|prep\tor|cc\tafter|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Spain is lagging behind in this area, which is a matter of great concern, with a relatively low enrolment rate and city pollution values exceeding those allowed at European level.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that Spain is lagging behind in this area?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Spain's pollution rate compared to European cities?",
                    "score": 0.7208,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tis|aux\tthat Spain is lagging behind in this area , which is a matter of great concern , with a relatively low enrolment rate and city pollution values exceeding those allowed at European level|ccomp\tthis|det\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\ta|det\t,|punct\ta|det\trelatively|advmod\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the enrolment rate in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.699,
                    "answers": "enrolment|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the pollution rate of Spain?",
                    "score": 0.6969,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Spain is lagging behind in this area , which is a matter of great concern , with a relatively low enrolment rate and city pollution values exceeding those allowed at European level|ROOT\ta matter of great concern|attr\tgreat concern|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the European level of pollution?",
                    "score": 0.6264,
                    "answers": "those allowed at European level|dobj\tallowed at European level|acl\tat European level|prep\tEuropean level|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There is an urgent need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehicles in our country, as well as to review car taxation to discourage the most polluting vehicles.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of vehicles did elpais.com report that there was an urgent need to review incentives for?",
                    "answer": "zero-emission vehicles"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the need to review incentives for the promotion of zero-emission vehicles?",
                    "score": 0.7613,
                    "answers": "urgent|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many polluting vehicles are polluting each year?",
                    "score": 0.7602,
                    "answers": "to discourage the most polluting vehicles|advcl\tmost polluting|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the polluting vehicle?",
                    "score": 0.6776,
                    "answers": "the most polluting vehicles|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "More and more brands  albeit unevenly developed  are slowly joining the electric automotive industry.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that More and more brands are slowly joining the electric automotive industry?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many new brands are entering the electric car industry?",
                    "score": 0.7923,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that More and more brands   albeit unevenly developed   are slowly joining the electric automotive industry|ROOT\ton 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tMore and more|amod\tand|cc\tmore|conj\tMore and more brands|nsubj\tthat More and more brands   albeit unevenly developed|dep\talbeit|mark\t |dep\tare|aux\tslowly|advmod\tare slowly joining the electric automotive industry|ccomp\tthe|det\tautomotive|amod\tthe electric automotive industry|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Innovation focuses on self-driving and traffic safety.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that Innovation focuses on self-driving and traffic safety?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the focus of Innovation on self-driving and traffic safety?",
                    "score": 0.7827,
                    "answers": "that Innovation focuses on self - driving and traffic safety|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5384,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\tand|cc\ttraffic|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5299,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Innovation focuses on self - driving and traffic safety|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The EU is, in fact, in the final stages of regulatory development in order to promote certain changes, for example, by increasing charging points, in the Community territory.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that the EU is in the final stages of regulatory development?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the EU doing to promote certain changes?",
                    "score": 0.7546,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that The EU is , in fact , in the final stages of regulatory development in order to promote certain changes , for example , by increasing charging points , in the Community territory|ROOT\tThe EU|nsubj\tthat The EU is , in fact , in the final stages of regulatory development in order to promote certain changes , for example , by increasing charging points , in the Community territory|ccomp\tin the final stages of regulatory development|prep\tthe final stages of regulatory development|pobj\torder to promote certain changes , for example , by increasing charging points , in the Community territory|pobj\tto promote certain changes , for example , by increasing charging points , in the Community territory|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many charging points does the EU have?",
                    "score": 0.7246,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tThe|det\tfinal|amod\tcharging|compound\tcharging points|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the charging points in the Community territory of the EU?",
                    "score": 0.6309,
                    "answers": "in the Community territory|prep\tthe Community territory|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the EU's regulatory development?",
                    "score": 0.629,
                    "answers": "of regulatory development|prep\tregulatory|amod\tregulatory development|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These innovations lead to disruption in the labour market where there will be challenges and opportunities.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that these innovations lead to disruption in the labour market?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many jobs are there in the labour market?",
                    "score": 0.783,
                    "answers": "labour|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many jobs were created in Africa in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.7095,
                    "answers": "that These innovations lead to disruption in the labour market where there will be challenges and opportunities|ccomp\twhere there will be challenges and opportunities|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the employment growth in South Africa in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.6766,
                    "answers": "These|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5153,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that These innovations lead to disruption in the labour market where there will be challenges and opportunities|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These are companies that are factories of ideas, with a tremendous vertical integration.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that these companies are factories of ideas?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of integration does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7543,
                    "answers": "vertical|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of business is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.7389,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tThese|nsubj\tthat These are companies that are factories of ideas , with a tremendous vertical integration|ccomp\tcompanies that are factories of ideas , with a tremendous vertical integration|attr\tthat|nsubj\tthat are factories of ideas , with a tremendous vertical integration|relcl\tfactories of ideas , with a tremendous vertical integration|attr\tof ideas|prep\tideas|pobj\t,|punct\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the vertical integration of companies that are factories of ideas?",
                    "score": 0.7364,
                    "answers": "with a tremendous vertical integration|prep\ttremendous|amod\ta tremendous vertical integration|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.552,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that These are companies that are factories of ideas , with a tremendous vertical integration|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Where a fuse can be the subject of discussion or the problem that must be solved and where they put their concentration hundreds of minds at once.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that where a fuse can be the subject of discussion or the problem that must be solved and where they put their concentration hundreds of minds at once?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of using a fuse to solve a problem?",
                    "score": 0.6119,
                    "answers": "their concentration|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about a fuse?",
                    "score": 0.6011,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tcan|aux\tthe|det\tdiscussion|pobj\tthe|det\tthat|nsubjpass\tof minds|prep\tminds|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of a fuse?",
                    "score": 0.5657,
                    "answers": "a|det\tmust|aux\tat once|prep\tonce|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a fuse and a problem that must be solved?",
                    "score": 0.5533,
                    "answers": "the problem that must be solved|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of where a fuse can be the subject of discussion and where it must be solved?",
                    "score": 0.5341,
                    "answers": "of discussion|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Where hope is shared.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/10/2017 that Where hope shared?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of where hope is shared?",
                    "score": 0.6623,
                    "answers": "on 23/10/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tWhere|advmod\thope|nsubjpass\tis|auxpass\tthat Where hope is shared|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4641,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 23/10/2017 that Where hope is shared|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}